Hi Vogue!
Come get ready with us for the challenge premiere.
No, one more time.
I haven't been on a set in a long time!
Hi Vogue!
Come get ready with us for the challenge premiere in Australia.
Come on!
It's a big night!
Oh, hi.
Didn't see you there.
What are we wearing?
I don't know.
How are you feeling?
Like, this is the first night.
Yeah.
The first, our first, uh, into the world of Challengers.
Challengers Universe.
This whole tennis thing is also more about a lifestyle, right?
Yeah, rather than a literal.
I think how she had, as they progressed and they got older, she had a
certain lifestyle.
You know what I mean?
I think that kind of plays into if she was a real person.
I don't know where to start.
I think for me it's either the way we start out with punching them in
the face or we start introducing this new character to the world.
It's our 13th year I think.
It's our 13th year of collage.
We don't miss.
We like Jordan and Pippin, baby.
Period.
All the things really I learned through fashion, I learned through you, so
here we are.
I'm your brightest pupil.
Became this beautiful canvas to help me express myself and let me become this
this.
Okay, girl.
She's not a poet.
She's a poet.
Sure.
Exactly.
We love a metaphor.
Yeah.
We want to make sure that we're giving the people that first write taste.
Yeah, of what we're planning for the rest of the tour.
That's why I dyed my hair, just so it felt like a different press store.
A little reset.
I typically don't like doing things like this because I'm very anxious and uncomfortable when
I'm getting ready, very quiet.
So if I'm over-talkative, that's because I'm anxious.
Hi, my name is Ursula Stephen, celebrity hairstylist.
Today we are going for the old money look.
Just very rich, well-to-do.
It's going to be big and sexy and, you know, we're going to have a
little fun.
What's the most intricate thing you have to do?
It's just going to be defining it.
We're going to do a really pretty sparkle situation, but just kind of defining that
it doesn't get lost.
What is Challengers about?
Three complicated people whose lives are intertwined and connected through tennis and
love and hate and all the things over many, many years.
Tashi is really the center of it all.
She's a go-getter.
She's extremely driven and kind of willing to do whatever is necessary to get out
of life what she needs.
I believe that tennis is her first love and the boys are just kind of
avenues for her to keep playing because she can't play herself.
I think, you know, people see me as a teenager since I was a teenager
for so long.
This is really finally me being able to play a woman closer to my own
age.
Well, technically I do still play a teenager at some points, but then she, you
know, she grows up.
But I think her unapologetic harshness, I think, is something I've never really played a
character like that before.
I also think she's like, sometimes she's the villain.
Once you see it, it'll make more sense why it's hard for me to describe
this woman.
It was really masterfully written by Justin Tritsky, who wrote a really brilliant
script.
It's just one of those scripts that, like, immediately I couldn't stop.
turning the page and wanting to know what happened to these characters.
So I felt like I knew it was something I wanted to be part of.
Literal.
Boom.
She's wearing custom Loewe.
Our costume designer.
Thank you.